backlinksgenius.com 2013-05-02

# Privacy statement | BackLinks Genius

Your privacy is important to BackLinks Genius Ltd. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that BackLinks Genius Ltd collects, and the ways in which BackLinks Genius Ltd uses that personal information.

## Personal information collection

BackLinks Genius Ltd may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

  * information about your use of this website;
  * information that you provide using for the purpose of registering with the website;
  * any other information that you send to BackLinks Genius Ltd.

## What we do not collect

  * financial details of our customers (like credit/debet cards, login details to PayPal and Moneybookers...)

## Using personal information

BackLinks Genius Ltd may use your personal information to:

  * administer this website;
  * personalize the website for you;
  * enable your access to and use of the website services;
  * publish information about you on the website;
  * send to you products that you purchase;
  * supply to you services that you purchase;
  * send you statements and invoices;
  * send you marketing communications.

Where BackLinks Genius Ltd discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, BackLinks Genius Ltd may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

## Securing your data

BackLinks Genius Ltd will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

BackLinks Genius Ltd will store all the personal information you provide on its secure servers.

Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this website will be  protected by encryption technology.

## Cross-border data transfers

Information that BackLinks Genius Ltd collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which BackLinks Genius Ltd operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available around the world.

You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

## What about "cookies?"

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our cookies do not store any personal information, but they do enable us to store your web site preferences and settings between visits.

## Updating this statement

BackLinks Genius may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website.

You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

## Other websites

This website contains links to other websites.

BackLinks Genius Ltd is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

## In summary

We are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect on the site to make your use of BackLinks Genius Ltd services possible and to enhance your user experience. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.

## Contact

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or BackLinks Genius treatment of your personal information, please write to:

  * by contact form or e-mail address published on Contact us page; or
  * by post to 2 TINTAGEL CLOSE, RUSHDEN, NORTHAMPTONSHIRE, UNITED KINGDOM.
